theeconomiccollapseblog.com 2014-06-25

# Website Privacy Policy

**Site Terms and Privacy Policy**

Site Terms

> Pictures and information on this blog are for commenting purposes only. We use images and information found on the web and consider to be in the public domain. We claim no ownership of them. We make no representations as to accuracy, completeness, currentness, suitability, or validity of any information on this site and will not be liable for any errors, omissions, or delays in this information or any losses, injuries, or damages arising from its display or use. If there is an image you don't want displayed on this site, please contact us using the contact form linked to at the top of the page and it will be deleted immediately.

I. LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This website has relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads and links on our pages. As a result of your visit to this website, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information.

Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving from this website to another website. We encourage you to read the site terms and privacy statements of these linked sites as their site terms and privacy policies may differ from ours.

The Economic Collapse Blog is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

II. ORDERS

If you purchase a product from one of the companies this site represents, they will request certain personally identifiable information from you on their order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This site is not responsible for the site terms or privacy policies of such other sites so review their site terms and privacy policy before completing your order.

Privacy Policy

CONSUMER PRIVACY

I. INFORMATION WE COLLECT: INDIVIDUAL INTERNET CONSUMERS

A. Personally Identifiable Information

Under no circumstances does this website request or collect sensitive personally identifiable information such as an Internet user’s medical/health conditions; racial or ethnic origin; political, religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations; trade union membership or sex life.

B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When a consumer responds to or views an Internet advertisement served by this website (such as through third-party websites or email solicitation) or visits an advertiser’s web site, we send a cookie and/or gif file ("Cookies") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the end user’s Internet browser. Cookies are small data files commonly used on the Internet to help optimize and personalize the Internet end user experience and identify repeat visitors to websites. This website uses Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of consumers and the services they select; and also to optimize and personalize the Internet user’s experience. If the Internet user re-visits the advertiser’s site directly, This website is able to continue to track the user’s activities. Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, and date/time stamp. We use the information to analyze site usage, administer the site, understand usage and navigation trends in aggregate, and determine the relevance of content. This information, however, is not linked to any personally identifiable information. We also may use Internet browsing and online purchase data associated with an anonymous identifier to develop a predictive statistical user profile of the end user’s needs and interests. This website does not use Cookies or log files to collect end users’ names, physical addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, credit card numbers, social security numbers, or any other information which can be used to identify a specific person. This website has relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads and links on our web pages. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Some of these other companies may use marketing technology that allows advertisers to add non-personally-identifying demographic information, such as age, gender, area code, or ZIP code, to the non-identifiable profile data. Thus, there is no direct connection between an end user’s online choices and his or her personal identity. In some cases, this website receives and records partial email addresses of Internet users, only in circumstances where the user voluntarily provided its identity and contact information through the advertiser’s site or third-party marketer’s site. This partial email address does not enable this website to personally identify an Internet rser nor is it shared, sold, rented, or given away.

II. INFORMATION SHARING

This website may release account and any other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law; or protect the rights, property, or safety of this website or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

III. CONSUMER CHOICE AND ACCESS

A. Opting Out.

Some Cookies have an “opt-out” option. This process does not remove this website's Cookie from your system; it simply replaces it with an opt-out Cookie that does not contain any unique identifiers. If this site provides such a process it is detailed below. Some of this website’s Cookies do not have an “opt-out” option, yet you still have the option of blocking the use of Cookies by changing a setting in your Internet browser. Please see your browser supplier’s Web site for details on how to do this. This site does not maintain a process for an individual consumer to opt-out of this website’s Cookies.

B. Accessing Consumer Information.

Because they are not directed towards individual Internet users, most sites do not maintain a process for an individual consumer to review and/or request changes to any personally identifiable information collected. Except as provided below, this site does not maintain a process for an individual consumer to access his or her personally identifiable information.

IV. SECURITY

This website employs industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data. Any data that is stored on this website’s servers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. This website allows access to this data only to those employees or third parties who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering this website’s products and services by means of user login and password requirements. No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of this website to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your information, this website cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with this website.

V. CONSENT AND CHANGES

This website may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by this website prior to the effective date of the policy change.

VI. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY AND SPAM

This website is very sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. It is possible that this website’s products and services may may not be appropriate for or directed at children. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to do business with us and we do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. This Site is committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. § 7701). It is our policy to prohibit the sending of unsolicited or “Spam” e-mail by this website or any of our marketing partners. Please note that under the CAN-SPAM Act, an advertiser is required to provide an opt-out mechanism for consumers to unsubscribe from future emails about the advertiser. Although not required to by law, many email marketers also include an opt-out mechanism to enable consumers to be removed from their mailing list. This has caused some confusion for consumers in opting out. The table below clarifies which opt-out mechanism you should use for commercial emails.

VII. DATA PROCESSING/SAFE HARBOR

The European Union maintains strict privacy laws. These rules differ significantly from US laws. To reconcile these differences, the US and the EU have created a Safe Harbor that defines mutually acceptable privacy operations. This website adheres to the Safe Harbor principals.

For more information see [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor).

VIII. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, THIRD PARTY INFORMATION & LANGUAGE

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR SITE TERMS (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES, AND ARBITRATION OF DISPUTES). YOU AGREE THAT THIS SITE’S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY THIS SITE OR $250 TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.

You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to this website with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party’s personal data has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s personal data; (c) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express will of the parties that this agreement and all related documents have been drawn up in English.

Updated 12/24/2009

Banner Photo Credits....

WallStreet Banner - From Dottorpeni on Flicker

Storm Picture By Mrpbps on Flicker

Glass Globe By From Some geekintn on Flicker

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
